thesocialtravelsummit.com 2019-03-07

# Privacy Policy • The Social Travel Summit The Social Travel Summit

**Commitment to User Privacy**

iambassador, the Organiser of The Social Travel Summit, is committed to protecting your privacy. You can visit most pages on this site without giving us any information about yourself. But sometimes we do need information to provide services that you request. This document is designed to give a clear explanation of iambassador‘s data processing practices. Please see below for further information.

Our website address is: https://thesocialtravelsummit.com.

If you have any questions or concerns relating to this site or would like to find out more about how we collect, store or use your personal data, please contact:

Keith Jenkins

Email: info@iambassador.net

**Who we are**

iambassador leverages a global network of professional travel influencers to produce innovative digital marketing campaigns, high-quality multimedia content, networking events, conferences and workshops/seminars. iambassador’s flagship conference The Social Travel Summit is an annual gathering of professional travel influencers and tourism industry partners from around the world. The aim of this conference is to present trends in digital marketing, highlight best practices, brainstorm new collaborative approaches via a series of keynotes, seminars, discussions and networking events. iambassador is based in Amsterdam, the Netherlands, and has representations in London, Cologne, Milan, Washington D.C. and Rio de Janeiro.

**What personal data we collect and why we collect it**

The personal information you provide in our contact form, registration or purchase of tickets is being collected for legitimate business purposes, which includes accessing/processing registrations or inquiries, keeping you informed about the conference and new events, and providing the best possible service to you. Whenever we process data for these purposes we will ensure that we always keep your Personal Data rights in high regard and take account of these rights.

The provision of this information is voluntary. However, if you do not provide the information requested, we may be unable to process your registration or inquiry. All information provided by you will be held in the strictest confidence.

We will only collect the personal information that is necessary for the purposes mentioned above. It includes the following (however is not limited to):

– Full Name & Job Title

– Company/Blog Name  

– Phone Number

– Email Address

– Social media channels and follower stats

iambassador is the sole owner of the information collected on this site.

_Comments_

When visitors leave comments on the site we collect the data shown in the comments form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it. The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: https://automattic.com/privacy/. After approval of your comment, your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

_Cookies_

When you visit this site, a cookie (a very small text file) is placed on your device. If you accept it, it is used to assist in the collection of the site visitation statistics. You may refuse the cookie, if you wish. To do so, you will need to check your browser settings.

iambassador collects certain information about your computer hardware and software, this includes (however is not limited to):

– IP Address

– Browser Type

– Operating System

– Access Times

– Referring Website Addresses

This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of iambassadors websites.

If you choose to not have your browser accept cookies, you will still be able to view the site.

If you leave a comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies. These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

_Embedded content from other websites_

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website.

These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

_Links to Other Websites_

This site contains some links to other sites. Please be aware that iambassador is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. This privacy statement applies solely to the information collected by iambassador.

_Surveys_

From time to time, iambassador may run surveys and may request information from users as part of these. Participation in these is entirely voluntary.

**Who we share your data with**

We do not rent or sell our customer e-mail lists. We may share your personal information with professional organisations (our event sponsors/exhibitors) to promote products and services related to your area of interest. If you do not consent to share your personal information with third party organisations please email info@iambassador.net.

_Transfer of Data_

The internet is a global environment. The data that we collect from you may be transferred to, and stored at, international destinations, including destinations outside the European Economic Area (“EEA”). It may also be processed by international staff or data processors outside this area, who may be engaged in, among other things, the fulfilment of your order, the processing of your payment details and the provision of support services.

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service.

iambassador will take all steps reasonably necessary to ensure that your data is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Notice.

If you do not consent to this transfer, storing or processing of your personal information please email info@iambassador.net indicating your wishes.

**Security**

iambassador takes precautions to protect your information. Access to all of our users’ information is restricted in our locations. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job are granted access to personally identifiable information. The servers that we store personally identifiable information on are kept in a secure environment.

**Correcting, Updating or Removing Your Personal Information**

If you have left comments, you can request to receive an exported file of the personal data we hold about you, including any data you have provided to us. You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes.

If your personal information is incorrect or if you no longer wish to receive information from iambassador, we will endeavour to correct, update or remove your information as swiftly as possible. This can be done by e-mailing info@iambassador.net.

If you no longer wish to receive newsletters or promotional materials, you may opt-out of receiving these communications. You can do it by following the unsubscribe link placed in the footer of the promotional email. 

**Data Storage and Retention**

The personal data we hold is stored on secured iambassador servers in the Netherlands and Italy and on the servers of cloud based database management services located in United States and Ireland. iambassador retains data for the duration of the customer’s or member’s business relationship with iambassador.

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue.

**GDPR Compliance**

iambassador respects your right to privacy. We ensure all data is managed lawfully, fairly and transparently. We use third parties such as Google Analytics and relevant social media platforms to also acquire data, we hold those parties to the same high standard.

All our users have the right to request their data and the right to be forgotten. For more information on where and how long your personal data is stored, and for more information on your rights of erasure, please contact Keith Jenkins by email: info@iambassador.net.

**Canada’s Anti-Spam Legislation**

iambassador has taken all reasonable steps to comply with Canada’s Anti-Spam Legislation. We only email contacts with whom we have had a business relationship within the last 2 years, individuals who may have inquired about an event in the last 6 months or who have opted in to receive our marketing communications. Should you receive an unsolicited email from iambassador, please click on ‘Unsubscribe’ in the footer, or email info@iambassador.net and we will remove your details within 48 hours.

**Notification of Changes**

iambassador reserves the right to amend the privacy notice. In such case the ‘last updated’ date will be amended accordingly and you will be informed via statement prominently displayed on the website.

Privacy Policy last updated on: 21st May 2018
